Dennis DeConcini Papers 1944-2008
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Congressional Activities. 1944-1998
  - Series 2: Legislative Committee Files. 1954-1994
    - Subseries 20: Veterans Affairs, 1970-1994
      - Veterans of Operation Desert Shield, Outbreak of Unknown Disease. 1992 (Box 320, Folder 26)
      - Veterans' Widows. 1982-1983 (Box 320, Folder 27)
      - Vietnam, Claims by American Citizens and Companies. 1985 (Box 320, Folder 28)
      - Vietnam, Medical Equipment Transfer. 1989 (Box 320, Folder 29)
      - Vietnam Trip, Senator DeConcini. 1986 (Box 320, Folder 30)
      - Vietnam Trip, Senator DeConcini. 1985-1986 (Box 320, Folder 31)
      - Vietnam Trip, Senator DeConcini. 1985-1986 (Box 321, Folder 1)
      - Vietnam Veterans of America. 1981-1987 (Box 321, Folder 2)
      - Vietnam Veterans Civic Council. 1981-1984 (Box 321, Folder 3)
      - Vietnam Veterans General. 1981 (Box 321, Folder 4)
      - Vietnam Veterans Leadership Program. 1982-1983 (Box 321, Folder 5)
      - Vietnam Veterans Memorial. 1981-1984 (Box 321, Folder 6)
      - Vietnam Veterans Memorial, Operation Freedom Bird. 1992-1993 (Box 321, Folder 7)
      - Vietnam Veterans Readjustment. 1985-1988 (Box 321, Folder 8)
      - War History, Korea, World War II, News Articles. 1991 (Box 321, Folder 9)
      - White House Conference on Veterans Act. 1981 (Box 321, Folder 10)
      - Williams Air Force Base. 1989 (Box 321, Folder 11)
      - Williams Air Force Base. 1990-1991 (Box 321, Folder 12)
      - Williams Air Force Base Closure. 1991-1993 (Box 321, Folder 13-14)
      - Women Veterans. 1987-1992 (Box 321, Folder 15)
      - World War I Veterans. 1979-1984 (Box 321, Folder 16)
      - World War II Veterans. 1986-1994 (Box 321, Folder 17)
      - World War II Veterans, Bushmasters Association. 1984-1988 (Box 321, Folder 18)
      - World War II Veterans, Bushmasters Association. 1988-1989 (Box 321, Folder 19)
  - Series 3: Bills, 1977-1994
    - Approval Forms. 1989 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Approval Forms. 1990 (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Approval Forms. 1991 (Box 322, Folder 3-4)
    - Approval Forms. 1992 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Approval Forms. 1993 (Box 322, Folder 6-7)
    - Approval Forms. 1994 (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - Congressional Immunity, General. 1978 (Box 322, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Record Notebooks, 95th Congress. 1977-1978 (Box 322, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Legislative. 1985-1994 (Box 322, Folder 11-12)
    - Correspondence, Memos-Staff. 1987-1993 (Box 322, Folder 13)
    - General. 1985-1994 (Box 322, Folder 14-15)
    - Legislation, Bilingual Courts Act. 1977 (Box 322, Folder 16)
    - Legislation, Bilingual Courts Act. 1979-1989 (Box 322, Folder 17)
    - Legislation, Private Bills. 1978-1979 (Box 322, Folder 18)
    - Legislation, Senate Bill Proposals. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Legislation, Senate Resolutions. 1980-1990 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, Sponsored Bills. 1977-1990 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Accomplishments-Baxter, Ed. 1985-1986 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Achievements-Brown, Shannon. 1993 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Achievements-Carlsgaard, Tim. 1987-1988 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Achievements-Conner, Lucy. 1984-1985 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Achievements-DeConcini, Dennis. 1982-1992 (Box 323, Folder 8-9)
    - Legislative Achievements-Fielder, Bob. 1985 (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Achievements-Flinn, Bruce. 1993 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Achievements-Green, Janie. 1985 (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Achievements-Hawkins, Mary. 1983-1994 (Box 323, Folder 13)
    - Legislative Achievements-Kimmerly, Lynn. 1990-1994 (Box 323, Folder 14)
    - Legislative Achievements-Lynch, Patty. 1985-1986 (Box 323, Folder 15)
    - Legislative Achievements-Magner, Jim. 1981-1984 (Box 323, Folder 16)
    - Legislative Achievements-Mills, Bobby. 1985 (Box 323, Folder 17)
    - Legislative Achievements-O'Leary, Michael. 1993 (Box 323, Folder 18)
    - Legislative Achievements-Roemer, Tim. 1985-1987 (Box 323, Folder 19-20)
    - Legislative Achievements-Schorr, Bobbie. 1993-1994 (Box 323, Folder 21)
    - Legislative Achievements-Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1983-1992 (Box 323, Folder 22-23)
    - Legislative Achievements-Senate, General. 1977 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Achievements-Swensen, Cele. 1985-1989 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Achievements-Tracy, June. 1985-1993 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Legislative, Achievements-Walgren, Chip. 1985-1994 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Legislative, Achievements-Walicki, Nancy. 1985 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 95th Congress. 1977-1978 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 96th Congress. 1979-1981 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 97th Congress. 1981-1983 (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 98th Congress. 1983-1984 (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 99th Congress. 1985-1987 (Box 324, Folder 10-11)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 100th Congress. 1987-1988 (Box 324, Folder 12-14)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 101st-102nd Congress. 1989-1991 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 102nd-103rd Congress. 1991-1993 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 103rd Congress. 1993 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Activities Report, 103rd Congress. 1993-1994 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Initiatives. 1991-1992 (Box 325, Folder 5)
  - Series 4: Voting Records, 1977-1994
    - Appropriations Bills, Roll Call Votes. 1978-1981 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Budget Resolution, FY. 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Committees, Appropriations. 1981-1992 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Committees, Judiciary. 1981-1992 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Committees, Indian Affairs. 1991-1993 (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - Committees, Rules. 1981-1992 (Box 325, Folder 11)
    - Committees, Veteran Affairs. 1981-1992 (Box 325, Folder 12)
    - Congressional Quarterly Weekly Report Vote Analysis. 1988-1992 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Contra Aid. 1989 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - DeConcini/Kennedy Comparison. 1989-1992 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Alternatives: A Look at the Record, Part II. 1984 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Vote Analyses. 1981 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Federal Assistance Award Report. 1989-1992 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Federal Assistance Award Report. 1993 (Box 326, Folder 7)
    - General. 1977-1993 (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - Individualized Voting Report, Appropriations. 1981-1993 (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - Individualized Voting Report, DeConcini/McCain Comparison. 1987-1991 (Box 326, Folder 10-11)
    - Individualized Voting Report, Defense. 1979-1992 (Box 326, Folder 12)
    - Individualized Voting Report, General. 1979-1991 (Box 326, Folder 13)
    - Individualized Voting Report, Quayle/Bentsen Comparison. 1988 (Box 326, Folder 14)
    - Individualized Voting Report, Various. 1979-1993 (Box 326, Folder 15)
    - Interest Groups, American Association of University Women. 1985-1987 (Box 326, Folder 16)
    - Interest Groups, American Security Council. 1978-1990 (Box 326, Folder 17)
    - Interest Groups, Analysis of Interest Group Ratings of Senators-Volume IX. 1992 (Box 326, Folder 18)
    - Interest Groups, Analysis of Interest Group Ratings of Senators-Volume X. 1993 (Box 326, Folder 19)
    - Interest Groups, Chamber of Commerce. 1978-1980 (Box 326, Folder 20)
    - Interest Groups, Council for a Livable World. 1982-1991 (Box 326, Folder 21)
    - Interest Groups, Federal Employees. 1978-1984 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Interest Groups, General. 1977-1992 (Box 327, Folder 2-4)
    - Interest Groups, Human Rights Campaign Fund. 1991-1992 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Interest Groups, Labor Groups. 1977-1993 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Interest Groups, League of Conservation Voters. 1981-1993 (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Interest Groups, NAACP. 1984 (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - Interest Groups, National Taxpayers Union Foundation. 1994 (Box 327, Folder 9)
    - Interest Groups, Ratings by Public Interest Groups. 1979-1982 (Box 327, Folder 10-15)
    - Roll Call Votes, Missed Votes. 1977-1979 (Box 327, Folder 16)
    - Roll Call Votes, Missed Votes. 1980-1981 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Roll Call Votes, Missed Votes. 1982-1984 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Roll Call Votes, Missed Votes. 1985-1993 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Roll Call Votes, Missed Votes, Patterns. 1979-1993 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Senate Close Votes. 1973-1982 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Senate Record Votes, 95th Congress, 1st Session. 1977 (Box 328, Folder 6-8)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 95th Congress-1st Session. 1977 (Box 328, Folder 9)
    - Senate Record Votes, 95th Congress-2nd Session. 1978 (Box 328, Folder 10-14)
    - Senate Record Votes, 96th Congress-1st Session. 1979 (Box 328, Folder 15-16)
    - Senate Record Votes, 96th Congress-1st Session. 1979 (Box 329, Folder 1-2)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 96th Congress-1st Session. 1979 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Senate Record Votes, 96th Congress-2nd Session. 1980 (Box 329, Folder 4-7)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 96th Congress-2nd Session. 1980 (Box 329, Folder 8)
    - Senate Record Votes, 97th Congress-1st Session. 1981 (Box 329, Folder 9-12)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 97th Congress-1st Session. 1981 (Box 329, Folder 13)
    - Senate Record Votes, 97th Congress-2nd Session. 1982 (Box 329, Folder 14)
    - Senate Record Votes, 97th Congress-2nd Session. 1982 (Box 330, Folder 1-3)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 97th Congress-2nd Session. 1982 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Senate Record Votes, 98th Congress-1st Session. 1983 (Box 330, Folder 5-7)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 98th Congress-1st Session. 1983 (Box 330, Folder 8)
    - Senate Record Votes, 98th Congress-2nd Session. 1984 (Box 330, Folder 9-11)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 98th Congress-2nd Session. 1984 (Box 330, Folder 12)
    - Senate Record Votes, 99th Congress-1st Session. 1985 (Box 330, Folder 13-14)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 99th Congress-1st Session. 1985 (Box 330, Folder 15)
    - Senate Record Votes, 99th Congress-2nd Session. 1986 (Box 330, Folder 16)
    - Senate Record Votes, 99th Congress-2nd Session. 1986 (Box 331, Folder 1-2)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 99th Congress-2nd Session. 1986 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Senate Record Votes, 100th Congress-1st Session. 1987 (Box 331, Folder 4-6)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 100th Congress-1st Session. 1987 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Senate Record Votes, 100th Congress-2nd Session. 1988 (Box 331, Folder 8-10)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 100th Congress-2nd Session. 1988 (Box 331, Folder 11)
    - Senate Record Votes, 101st Congress-1st Session. 1989 (Box 331, Folder 12-14)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 101st Congress-1st Session. 1989 (Box 331, Folder 15)
    - Senate Record Votes, 101st Congress-2nd Session. 1990 (Box 331, Folder 16)
    - Senate Record Votes, 101st Congress-2nd Session. 1990 (Box 332, Folder 1-2)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 101st Congress-2nd Session. 1990 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Senate Record Votes, 102nd Congress-1st Session. 1991 (Box 332, Folder 4-5)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 102nd Congress-1st Session. 1991 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Senate Record Votes, 102nd Congress-2ndSession. 1992 (Box 332, Folder 7-8)
    - Senate Record Votes, DeConcini, Dennis, 102nd Congress-2ndSession. 1992 (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - Senate Record Votes, 103rd Congress-1st Session. 1993 (Box 332, Folder 10-12)
    - Senate Record Votes, 103rd Congress-2nd Session. 1994 (Box 332, Folder 13-14)
    - Social Security Votes. 1979-1993 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Tax Votes. 1979-1993 (Box 333, Folder 2)
  - Series 5: Speech Files, 1977-1994
    - Abortion. 1981-1983 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture. 1979-1994 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Armed Forces. 1982-1992 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Arms Control. 1979-1994 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Banking. 1984-1988 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Bankruptcy. 1983-1989 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Budget. 1981-1990 (Box 333, Folder 9-12)
    - Business. 1979-1990 (Box 333, Folder 13)
    - Children. 1979-1990 (Box 333, Folder 14)
    - Children. 1979-1990 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Copyrights. 1982-1989 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Crime. 1979-1994 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - DeConcini, Susan. 1977-1984 (Box 334, Folder 4-5)
    - Defense. 1981-1994 (Box 334, Folder 6-8)
    - Democratic Party. 1978-1990 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Domestic Policy. 1988-1989 (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - Drugs. 1978-1992 (Box 334, Folder 11-14)
    - Economy. 1977-1993 (Box 335, Folder 1-3)
    - Education. 1979-1989 (Box 335, Folder 4-5)
    - Elderly. 1977-1992 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Energy. 1977-1993 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Environment. 1977-1994 (Box 335, Folder 8-11)
    - Equal Rights. 1977-1984 (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - Ethnic Groups. 1979-1993 (Box 335, Folder 13-14)
    - Ethnic Groups. 1979-1993 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Finance. 1979-1994 (Box 336, Folder 2-4)
    - Firearms. 1984-1988 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Floor Statements. 1979-1980 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - General. 1968-1980 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Government. 1978-1993 (Box 336, Folder 8-14)
    - Government, 95th Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Government, 96th Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Government, 97th Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Government, 98th Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Government, 99th Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Government, 100th Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Government, 101st Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Government, 102nd Congress-Congressional Speech Records. 1993 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Health Care. 1979-1992 (Box 337, Folder 9-11)
    - Housing. 1977-1988 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - Human Rights. 1979-1990 (Box 337, Folder 13)
    - Immigration. 1977-1989 (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - Index. 1977-1994 (Box 337, Folder 15)
    - Indian Affairs. 1979-1989 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - International Relations. 1977-1992 (Box 337, Folder 17)
    - International Relations. 1977-1992 (Box 338, Folder 1-9)
    - Judiciary. 1977-1994 (Box 338, Folder 10-12)
    - Judiciary. 1977-1994 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Law Enforcement. 1979-1993 (Box 339, Folder 2-3)
    - Legislation. 1984-1992 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Parks and Recreation. 1984-1993 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Public Service Announcements. 1980-1990 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Social Security. 1977-1987 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Social Services. 1983-1992 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Special Events. 1977-1994 (Box 339, Folder 9-14)
    - Taxation. 1978-1992 (Box 339, Folder 15)
    - Taxation. 1978-1992 (Box 340, Folder 1-3)
    - Technology. 1983-1989 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Trade. 1977-1993 (Box 340, Folder 5-7)
    - Transportation. 1982-1989 (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - Veterans. 1981-1993 (Box 340, Folder 9-11)
    - Youth. 1977-1993 (Box 340, Folder 12)
  - Series 6: Staff Files, 1972-1998
    - Subseries 1: Administrative Staff Files, 1977-1994
      - Abruscato, Anne Marie. 1992-1994 (Box 340, Folder 13-14)
      - Dill, Barry. 1989-1992 (Box 341, Folder 1)
      - Hamburger, Irene. 1987-1994 (Box 341, Folder 2)
      - Karp, Gene-Correspondence. 1977-1993 (Box 341, Folder 3)
      - Karp, Gene-Memorandum. 1977-1978 (Box 341, Folder 4)
      - Karp, Gene-Memorandum. 1979 (Box 341, Folder 5-6)
      - Karp, Gene-Memorandum. 1980 (Box 341, Folder 7)
      - Karp, Gene-Memorandum. 1981-1992 (Box 341, Folder 8)
      - Leiby, Judy. 1986 (Box 341, Folder 9)
      - Maynes, Bob. 1980-1987 (Box 341, Folder 10)
      - Miller, Steve. 1977-1986 (Box 341, Folder 11)
      - Nelson, Sharon-General. 1978-1986 (Box 341, Folder 12)
      - Ober, Ron. 1977-1993 (Box 341, Folder 13)
      - Siegel, Larry. 1984 (Box 341, Folder 14)
      - Turner, Virginia. 1989 (Box 341, Folder 15)
      - Altier, Mike. 1978-1980 (Box 341, Folder 16)
    - Subseries 2: Legislative Aide Files, 1977-1994
      - Balmuth, Cindy. 1994 (Box 341, Folder 17)
      - Baxter, Ed-Memoranda. 1982-1985 (Box 341, Folder 18)
      - Baxter, Ed-Memoranda. 1986-1990 (Box 342, Folder 1)
      - Bedford, Tara. 1993-1994 (Box 342, Folder 2)
      - Blaskowsky, Cliff. 1993-1994 (Box 342, Folder 3)
      - Bonham, Jerry-Memoranda. 1977-1979 (Box 342, Folder 4)
      - Bonham, Jerry-Memoranda. 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folder 5)
      - Bonham, Jerry-Memoranda. 1982 (Box 342, Folder 6)
      - Brown, Sally. 1990-1993 (Box 342, Folder 7)
      - Brown, Shannon-Memoranda. 1992-1994 (Box 342, Folder 8-9)
      - Burke, Dennis. 1989-1993 (Box 342, Folder 10)
      - Cocozza, Dick. 1987-1988 (Box 342, Folder 11)
      - Carlsgaard, Tim. 1987-1989 (Box 342, Folder 12-15)
      - Cobb, Cybele. 1990-1991 (Box 342, Folder 16)
      - Collins, Matt. 1993 (Box 342, Folder 17)
      - Conner, Lucy. 1982-1986 (Box 342, Folder 18)
      - Conner, Lucy. 1982-1986 (Box 343, Folder 1)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1977-1979 (Box 343, Folder 2)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1980 (Box 343, Folder 3)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1981 (Box 343, Folder 4-5)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1982-1983 (Box 343, Folder 6)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1984-1985 (Box 343, Folder 7)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1986-1989 (Box 343, Folder 8)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1990 (Box 343, Folder 9)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1991 (Box 343, Folder 10)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1992 (Box 343, Folder 11)
      - DeConcini, Dennis-Communication. 1993-1994 (Box 343, Folder 12)
      - De Leon, Lewis. 1993-1994 (Box 343, Folder 13)
      - Fielder, Bob. 1977-1986 (Box 343, Folder 14-15)
      - Ferry, Doug. 1993 (Box 343, Folder 16)
      - Flinn, Bruce. 1993 (Box 343, Folder 17)
      - Fisher, Jane. 1987-1994 (Box 343, Folder 18)
      - Fisher, Jane. 1987-1994 (Box 344, Folder 1)
      - Gearan, Tim. 1987 (Box 344, Folder 2)
      - Gearan, Tim. 1988-1989 (Box 344, Folder 3)
      - Gearan, Tim. 1990-1991 (Box 344, Folder 4)
      - Gearan, Tim. 1992 (Box 344, Folder 5)
      - Gearan, Tim. 1993-1994 (Box 344, Folder 6)
      - Green, Jane. 1979-1982 (Box 344, Folder 7)
      - Green, Jane. 1983-1985 (Box 344, Folder 8)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1978-1980 (Box 344, Folder 9)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1981 (Box 344, Folder 10)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1982-1983 (Box 344, Folder 11)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1984 (Box 344, Folder 12)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1985 (Box 344, Folder 13-15)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1986 (Box 345, Folder 1-2)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1987 (Box 345, Folder 3)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1988 (Box 345, Folder 4-5)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1989 (Box 345, Folder 6-7)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1990 (Box 345, Folder 8-9)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1991 (Box 345, Folder 10-11)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1992 (Box 345, Folder 12)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1993 (Box 345, Folder 13)
      - Hawkins, Mary. 1994 (Box 345, Folder 14)
      - Josephson, Jessica. 1981 (Box 345, Folder 15)
      - Kimmerly, Lynn. 1987-1990 (Box 346, Folder 1)
      - Kimmerly, Lynn. 1991-1992 (Box 346, Folder 2)
      - Kimmerly, Lynn. 1993-1994 (Box 346, Folder 3)
      - Long, Janis. 1990-1994 (Box 346, Folder 4)
      - Lopez, Rosalis. 1990-1992 (Box 346, Folder 5)
      - Lynch, Patty. 1978-1986 (Box 346, Folder 6)
      - Lynch, Patty. 1987-1988 (Box 346, Folder 7)
      - Lynch, Patty. 1989-1994 (Box 346, Folder 8)
      - Magner, Jim. 1977-1980 (Box 346, Folder 9)
      - Magner, Jim. 1981-1983 (Box 346, Folder 10)
      - McCoy, Matt. 1987-1989 (Box 346, Folder 11)
      - McMahon, Tara. 1987-1989 (Box 346, Folder 12)
      - McNaughton, Jeanne. 1985-1988 (Box 346, Folder 13)
      - McPike, Tim. 1977-1982 (Box 346, Folder 14)
      - Mills, Bobby. 1981-1984 (Box 346, Folder 15)
      - Mills, Bobby. 1985 (Box 346, Folder 16)
      - Mills, Bobby. 1986-1988 (Box 347, Folder 1)
      - Mulkey, John. 1977-1980 (Box 347, Folder 2)
      - Mulkey, John. 1981 (Box 347, Folder 3)
      - Mulkey, John. 1982 (Box 347, Folder 4)
      - O'Leary, Michael. 1993-1994 (Box 347, Folder 5)
      - Robb, Karen. 1990-1993 (Box 347, Folder 6)
      - Roemer, Tim. 1985-1986 (Box 347, Folder 7)
      - Roemer, Tim. 1987 (Box 347, Folder 8-10)
      - Roemer, Tim. 1988-1989 (Box 347, Folder 11)
      - Romani, Romano. 1975-1977 (Box 347, Folder 12)
      - Romani, Romano. 1978 (Box 347, Folder 13)
      - Romani, Romano. 1979 (Box 347, Folder 14)
      - Romani, Romano. 1980 (Box 347, Folder 15)
      - Romani, Romano. 1981 (Box 347, Folder 16)
      - Romani, Romano. 1982-1983 (Box 347, Folder 17)
      - Schorr, Bobbie. 1990-1992 (Box 348, Folder 1)
      - Schorr, Bobbie. 1993-1994 (Box 348, Folder 2)
      - Scott, Nancy. 1987-1989 (Box 348, Folder 3)
      - Scott, Susan. 1990-1993 (Box 348, Folder 4)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1979-1982 (Box 348, Folder 5)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1983 (Box 348, Folder 6)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1984 (Box 348, Folder 7)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1985 (Box 348, Folder 8)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1986 (Box 348, Folder 9)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1987 (Box 348, Folder 10-12)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1988 (Box 348, Folder 13)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1989 (Box 348, Folder 14-15)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1990 (Box 348, Folder 16)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1991 (Box 349, Folder 1)
      - Sedlmayr, Laurie. 1992-1994 (Box 349, Folder 2)
      - Shay, John. 1992 (Box 349, Folder 3)
      - Silver, Diane. 1989-1992 (Box 349, Folder 4)
      - Sissons, Eddie. 1989-1992 (Box 349, Folder 5)
      - Staff Meeting Minutes. 1979-1987 (Box 349, Folder 6)
      - Staff Meeting Minutes. 1988-1990 (Box 349, Folder 7)
      - Staff Meeting Minutes. 1991-1994 (Box 349, Folder 8)
      - States, Sally. 1989 (Box 349, Folder 9)
      - Steele, David. 1985-1988 (Box 349, Folder 10)
      - Steele, David. 1989 (Box 349, Folder 11-12)
      - Steele, David. 1990 (Box 349, Folder 13)
      - Steele, David. 1991-1992 (Box 349, Folder 14)
      - Steele, David. 1993-1994 (Box 349, Folder 15)
      - Swensen, Cele. 1982-1994 (Box 349, Folder 16)
      - Tarazon, Fred. 1980-1986 (Box 349, Folder 17)
      - Tracy, June. 1983-1988 (Box 349, Folder 18)
      - Tracy, June. 1989-1990 (Box 350, Folder 1)
      - Tracy, June. 1991-1992 (Box 350, Folder 2)
      - Tracy, June. 1993-1994 (Box 350, Folder 3)
      - Vincent, Duane. 1993 (Box 350, Folder 4)
      - Walgreen, Chip. 1985-1987 (Box 350, Folder 5)
      - Walgreen, Chip. 1988 (Box 350, Folder 6)
      - Walgreen, Chip. 1989 (Box 350, Folder 7)
      - Walgreen, Chip. 1990 (Box 350, Folder 8)
      - Walgreen, Chip. 1991-1992 (Box 350, Folder 9-10)
      - Walgreen, Chip. 1993-1994 (Box 350, Folder 11)
      - Wilcox, Mary Rose. 1979-1981 (Box 350, Folder 12)
      - Wolicki, Nancy. 1979-1980 (Box 350, Folder 13)
    - Subseries 3: Office Management Files, 1972-1994
      - Congressional Handbooks. 1972-1988 (Box 350, Folder 14)
      - Furniture/ Furnishing Selection. 1991 (Box 350, Folder 15)
      - General. 1979-1990 (Box 350, Folder 16)
      - Interns, General. 1983-1992 (Box 350, Folder 17)
      - Interns, Law School Internship Program. 1977-1987 (Box 350, Folder 18)
      - Interns, Senior Citizen Internship Program. 1984-1986 (Box 350, Folder 19)
      - Interns, Washington Summer Experiential Education Program. 1984-1992 (Box 350, Folder 20)